A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 1 FA1292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Grants, 1951-1996, 2002; 2
  - 59-520, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1960-1961 (Box 106, Folder 1797)
  - 61-592, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1961-1962 (Box 106, Folder 1798)
  - 62-648, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1961-1963 (Box 106, Folder 1799)
  - 63-695, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1963-1964 (Box 106, Folder 1800)
  - 64-763, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1964-1966 (Box 106, Folder 1801)
  - 65-835, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1965-1966 (Box 106, Folder 1802)
  - 66-897, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1966-1967 (Box 106, Folder 1803)
  - 68-023, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1967-1969 (Box 107, Folder 1804)
  - 69-087, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1968-1970 (Box 107, Folder 1805-1806)
  - 69-940, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 1807)
  - 71-201, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1971-1973 (Box 107, Folder 1808)
  - 72-267, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1972-1973, 1979-1982, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 1809)
  - 81-397, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1982, 1984-1986 (Box 108, Folder 1810)
  - Alan Gregg Fellowships, 1959-1974, 2002 (Box 108, Folder 1811-1812)
  - Fellowships, A-H, 1964-1974 (Box 108, Folder 1813-1815)
  - Fellowships, I-Z, 1964-1977 (Box 109, Folder 1816-1821)
  - Fellowships, Unallocated, 1965-1973 (Box 110, Folder 1822)
  - Administration, Office Budgets, 1964-1971 (Box 110, Folder 1823-1824)
- Member and Officer Files, 1923-2001; 3
  - Aldrich, Winthrop W., 1930-1932, 1934, 1938 (Box 110, Folder 1825)
  - Austin, Chellis A., 1928-1930 (Box 110, Folder 1826)
  - Bixby, Harold M., 1944-1947 (Box 110, Folder 1827)
  - Buchanan, J. Robert, 1969-1973, 1975-1987, 1989, 1997-1998, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 1828)
  - Buchanan, J. Robert, General, 1975, 1979, 1982, 1984-1986, 1988-2000 (Box 110, Folder 1829-1830)
  - Buchanan, J. Robert, China Medical Board (CMB) Trips: 1971, 1980, 1992, 1998, 1971-1972, 1980, 1992, 1998-2000 (Box 110, Folder 1831)
  - Buek, Charles W., Trustee, 1964-1980, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 1832)
  - Cannon, Walter B., 1939-1945 (Box 111, Folder 1833)
  - Catlin, Loring, General, 1978-1981, 1985, 1987-1992, 1997-1999 (Box 111, Folder 1834)
  - Catlin, Loring, China Medical Board (CMB) Trips: 1989, 1992, 1995, 1989, 1991-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 111, Folder 1835)
  - Catlin, Loring, Curriculum Vitae & Elections, 1976-1991, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 1836)
  - Cohn, Alfred E., 1934-1945, 1951, 1957 (Box 111, Folder 1837)
  - Connell, Frank H., Director (Associate), 1959-1963 (Box 111, Folder 1838-1840)
  - Connell, Frank H., Director (Associate), 1962-1970 (Box 112, Folder 1839-1846)
  - Connell, Frank H., Director (Associate), 1960-1961, 1963-1974, 1976-1978 (Box 113, Folder 1846-1847)
  - Coye, Molly Joel, General, 1989, 1994-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 113, Folder 1848)
  - Coye, Molly Joel, Curriculum Vitae & Elections, 1989, 1992, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 1849)
  - Drorbaugh, James E., Associate Director, 1969-1974 (Box 113, Folder 1850-1852)
  - Drorbaugh, James E., Regional Representative, 1972, 1975 (Box 113, Folder 1853)
  - Drorbaugh, James E., Regional Representative, 1974-1975 (Box 114, Folder 1854-1856)
  - Drorbaugh, James E., Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 114, Folder 1857)
  - Ecker, Frederic W., 1947-1964 (Box 114, Folder 1858-1859)
  - Eggleston, Margery K., 1923-1928, 1930, 1932-1938, 1941-1944, 1947-1948, 1951, 1954-1956, 1962, 1968-1969, 1972-1973 (Box 114, Folder 1860)
  - Ehlers, Walter G., General, 1983-1985, 1987-1992, 1995-2001 (Box 115, Folder 1861)
  - Elliott, Lloyd W., 1955-1971 (Box 115, Folder 1862)
  - Ellis, Mary, Secretary, 1970-1972, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 1863)
  - Ferguson, Mary E., 1961, 1969, 1971-1975, 1979-1980, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 1864)
  - Forkner, Claude E., 1942-1944 (Box 115, Folder 1865-1868)
  - Forkner, Claude E., 1943-1946, 1949, 1951, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 1869-1870)
  - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1927-1928, 1930, 1933-1945, 1956, 1967, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 1871)
  - Greene, Roger S., Director, 1928-1941 (Box 116, Folder 1872-1874)
  - Greene, Roger S., Director, 1942-1945, 1947 (Box 117, Folder 1875)
  - Greene, Roger S., Director, Resignation, 1934-1935 (Box 117, Folder 1876)
  - Greene, Roger S., Director, General, 1929, 1932-1936 (Box 117, Folder 1877)
  - Gregg, Alan G., 1933-1934, 1936-1939, 1942-1945, 1951, 1953-1959 (Box 117, Folder 1878-1879)
  - Griffing, Elizabeth B., Assistant Treasurer, 1967 (Box 117, Folder 1880)
  - Gumbel, Robert W., 1934-1935 (Box 117, Folder 1881)
  - Hart, Boies C., 1944-1945 (Box 117, Folder 1882)
  - Haskins, Lathrop S., 1962-1971 (Box 117, Folder 1883)
  - Herod, William R., 1947-1956, 1960, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 1884)
  - Herod, William R., 1958-1972 (Box 118, Folder 1885)
  - Hinsey, Joseph C., Chairman, 1944-156, 1971, 1976-1977, 1983-1984 (Box 118, Folder 1886)
  - Hogness, John R., Curriculum Vitae and Elections, 1967, 1969, 1971-1972, 1975, 1978, 1981-1989, 1991-1992 (Box 118, Folder 1887)
  - Hogness, John R., 1982-1984 (Box 118, Folder 1888)
  - Houghton, Henry S., 1934-1941, 1951-1954, 1956-1957, 1959-1962, 1964-1966, 1968, 1972, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 1889-1891)
  - Keefer, Chester S., 1944-1968, 1970-1972 (Box 119, Folder 1892-1893)
  - Kennedy, Isabel J., Assistant Treasurer, 1962-1967 (Box 119, Folder 1894)
  - Latourette, Kenneth S., 1934-1949, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 1895)
  - Lobenstine, Edwin C., 1935-1936, 1939-1945, 1947, 1950, 1956 (Box 119, Folder 1896)
  - Locke, Edwin A., Jr., Trustee, 1947-1953, 1950-1953, 1970-1980, 1985-1986 (Box 119, Folder 1897)
  - Loucks, Harold H., 1946-1949 (Box 119, Folder 1898-1901)
  - Loucks, Harold H., 1950-1958 (Box 120, Folder 1902-1908)
  - Loucks, Harold H., 1958 (Box 121, Folder 1909)
  - Loucks, Harold H., Director, 1949, 1954, 1958-1962, 1974-1980, 1982 (Box 121, Folder 1910-1911)
  - 59-490, Loucks, Harold H., Consultant, 1959-1960 (Box 121, Folder 1912)
  - Mallory, Walter H., 1947-1958, 1960-1961, 1963-1971 (Box 121, Folder 1913-1914)
  - Mathey, Dean, 1947-1957, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 1915)
  - McCoy, Oliver R., Director (Associate), Report on Korea, 1956 April 23-May 5 (Box 121, Folder 1916)
  - McCoy, Oliver R., Director (Associate), 1955-1958 (Box 121, Folder 1917-1919)
  - McCoy, Oliver R., Director (Associate), 1959 (Box 122, Folder 1920)
  - McCoy, Oliver R., Director, 1960-1964 (Box 122, Folder 1921-1926)
  - McCoy, Oliver R., Director, 1964-1969 (Box 123, Folder 1927-1931)
  - McCoy, Oliver R., President (Elected 1969 November 12) (Box 123, Folder 1932)
  - McCoy, Oliver R., President, 1969-1973 (Box 123, Folder 1933-1935)
  - McCoy, Oliver R., President, 1960-1962, 1964-1978, 1982, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 1936-1938)
  - Meyer, John M., 1957-1962 (Box 124, Folder 1939)
  - Monroe, Paul, 1928-1934 (Box 124, Folder 1940)
  - Moore, Robert A., 1955-1971 (Box 124, Folder 1941-1942)
  - Ongley, Patrick, Burma, 1975-1977 (Box 124, Folder 1943)
  - Ongley, Patrick, Burma, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 125, Folder 1944-1945)
  - Parker, Philo W., 1936-1946 (Box 125, Folder 1946-1948)
  - Parker, Philo W., 1947-1971, 1981 (Box 126, Folder 1949-1954)
  - Pearce, Agnes M., Secretary, 1936-1937, 1945, 1958-1958, 1963, 1966, 1970, 1974 (Box 126, Folder 1955)
  - Pearce, Richard M., 1928-1931 (Box 126, Folder 1956)
  - Potts, James E., 1969, 1971, 1974, 1976-1978, 1980-1981, 1984 (Box 126, Folder 1957)
  - Richardson, Willard S., 1933, 1935, 1952 (Box 126, Folder 1958)
  - Robinson, Edward, Treasurer, 1932-1941 (Box 126, Folder 1959)
  - Robinson, Edward, Treasurer, 1942-1947 (Box 127, Folder 1960)
  - Robinson, G. Canby, 1936-1943 (Box 127, Folder 1961-1968)
  - Robinson, G. Canby, 1944-1945, 1947, 1955-1956, 1960 (Box 128, Folder 1969)
  - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd, 1930-1947, 1950, 1952-1959, 1960-1962, 1966, 1978 (Box 128, Folder 1970-1976)
  - Sawyer, William D., 1987, 1989-1993, 1995-1999 (Box 129, Folder 1980-1981)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1928-1930 (Box 129, Folder 1982)
  - Sturgis, Henry S., 1947-1958, 1960-1961, 1963, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1983)
  - Trask, Frederick K., Jr., 1956-1977 (Box 129, Folder 1984)
  - Trippe, Juan, 1957-1971 (Box 129, Folder 1985)
  - van Dyke, Harry B., 1944-1962, 1968-1969 (Box 129, Folder 1986)
  - Vincent, George E., 1930, 1932-1934 (Box 129, Folder 1987)
  - Vincent, George E., 1932, 1934-1941 (Box 130, Folder 1988)
  - Weinberg, John L., 1970-1973, 1975-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1989)
  - Weldon, Virginia V., 1999 (Box 130, Folder 1990)
  - Wescoe, W. Clarke, Chancellor, University of Kansas, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 1991)
  - Wescoe, W. Clarke, President, 1968-1969 (Box 130, Folder 1992)
  - Wharton, Dolores D., 1976-1981, 1985 (Box 130, Folder 1993)
  - Boontong, Tassana, Employee, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 1994)
  - Eamjoy, Wanpen, Employee, 1979-1980 (Box 130, Folder 1995)
  - Manning, Elizabeth J. B., Employee, 1978-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1996)
  - Srisupan, Wichit, Employee, 1979 (Box 130, Folder 1997)